do you guys ever think about monsters inc and how these like relatively normal people clocked in
clocked out every single day when their entire career was terror their whole job the entire
the only job was to terrify children scare children they literally captured the screams
of children in these little canisters and then counted them up to compete for the highest scare
total and you look at these funny guys and you go like they don't look evil they look like nice
sort of funny goofy guys so what could compel them to terrorize children for a living particularly
when it's this blatant children scared scared totals and they put the screams in the little
canisters like there is no ambiguity about it right and there's no ambiguity about whether or not this
would be considered terror in real in the real world so how do they get these guys to do this
pure unholy terror look at his eyes he's like 10 times her size up on the bench pressed up against
the wall terrified of of who oh her her little baby boo so how do we teach this big strong guy to be
this scared of this little girl well this is really helpful the cda child detection agency who are here
for your safety sorry sir you have a tiny baby's sock on your back it's an emergency because of a
baby sock he feels scared for his own safety and for the safety of his community if this is the
response to a baby sock are you going to believe that that baby sock is life-threatening to you
extremely dangerous yes this is treated like an emergency they had to blow it up they had to blow
it up for safety to protect their people right and this poor guy so they put on displays like that for
their community to reinforce and remind the idea remind you of the fear the ever-present threat to
your safety to your children's safety and they have to instill this level of fear in their citizens
to ensure that they go nowhere near the children you do not go near the children unless you are literally
doing your job of scaring them right because if you get too close it all starts to unravel the
propaganda starts to unravel the child is not a threat the child is not dangerous the child is a
child the child is no threat to your personal safety the child is no threat to your community's
safety you are only taught to see the child as a threat because these numbers are money the powers
that be get people like this to scare babies like this by making them this scared using some of these
tools in order to keep these numbers high to make money for these people and the girls who get it get it
anyway free palestine